[theme music]
I cooked you lunch.
Oh, Michelle, you are
the sweetest girl in the world.
I know, eat it.
Okay.
Mm, I taste bananas
and...pickles and Jell-O.
- Or a bubble gum.
- 'Mm-hmm.'
You got all four food groups.
Hey, don't play
with your food.
Oh, nuts.
[Jesse Frederick singing
"Everywhere You Look"]
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Whatever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milk man
the paper boy evenin' TV ♪
♪ Ah ah ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold on to ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ There's a face ♪
♪ Of somebody
who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waiting
to carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ And everywhere you look ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-dow ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Alright, munchkins, we got
your chocolate moo juice here.
Extra chocolate,
easy on the moo.
Thanks, Uncle Jesse.
- Hey, everybody.
- 'Hey, Joey.'
- Guess what, Michelle.
I got you a tape
of children's songs by Raffi.
Thank you. What is a Raffi?
Well, he's the guy
who sings "Baby Beluga."
Oh, I used to love that song.
Dad, remember our dance?
Come on, let's show Michelle.
Oh, oh, this'll be fun.
I'll just put it here
in your little baby boom box.
Okay, Joey, rock 'n' roll.
[Raffi singing "Baby Beluga"]
♪ Baby Beluga
in the deep blue sea ♪
♪ He swims so wild
and he swims so free ♪
♪ Heaven above
and the sea below ♪
♪ And a little white whale
on the go two three four ♪
♪ Baby Beluga ♪
♪ Is the water cold ♪
♪ Is your mama home with you ♪
♪ So happy ♪
♪ Way down yonder
where the dolphins play.. ♪♪
This is great,
I got the "Baby Beluga" dancers
I'm drinking moo juice.
When did my life
become a G-rated movie?
- 'Hi.'
- Bye.
Girls, wait. How about a little,
"Hello, how was your day?"
No time to talk.
We're in charge of a dance.
What about your homework?
If we do our homework now
what do we do
while they take attendance?
Don't worry about me,
I'm almost finished.
Oh, yeah? Let's see it then.
Did I say almost finished?
I meant almost started.
Great. The dance is next Friday.
Don't be late.
- Dog Face said yes.
- Alright, we got a band.
Dog Face? Never heard of them.
That's because
you're in second grade
and Dog Face
is a high school band.
So? The Rolling Stones are about
a 100 and I've heard of them.
So what's next on our list?
Well, this is a backwards dance.
That means we have to get some
guys to be our dates.
Call up Kevin.
I can't right now.
I don't have his phone number.
Yes, you do,
it's a speed-dial button
with the heart drawn around it.
- Stephanie!
- It's ringing.
This is the phone company.
Your phone works fine. Goodbye.
[clucking]
[laughs]
- Kimmy.
- Sorry.
But sometimes she's funny.
- Hello, Kevin?
- Stephanie!
This is Stephanie Tanner
and I was wondering
if you'd like to
go to the backwards dance
with my lovely sister, D.J.?
I'm gonna kill you.
Okay, bye.
Kevin said yes.
I'm gonna hug you.
Teenagers..
You make such a big deal
out of everything.
[piano music]
Somebody do something!
It's been one solid week
of "Baby Beluga."
I'm going bananas!
♪ Baby Beluga ♪
♪ Oh Baby Beluga.. ♪♪
Joey, you gave her that tape,
you take it away.
Michelle, what do you say
we fast-forward
this thing to another song, huh?
No.
Well, Baby Beluga's tired.
He needs a nap.
Don't make me cry.
Ahem. How do I look?
[cheering]
You look great.
Dad, do you have to tape
everything?
Oh, sorry. Okay, I'll stop.
Well, maybe a few more seconds.
I'm having
a really good hair day.
[doorbell rings]
- I'll get it.
- Wait, that's Kevin!
Now.
Hi, neighbors. Hi, camera.
♪ I got the right stuff
oh oh oh.. ♪♪
Alright, Kimmy, uh, I gotta save
the batteries for later.
D.J., bad news.
We don't have a band.
Dog Face broke up.
This is terrible.
I promised
we'd have a great band.
Everybody's gonna hate me.
Unless..
W-w-what? What unless?
What are you looking at me for?
Oh, come on.
D.J., you know,
I-I'd be happy to help you out
but I can't get my band
at this late notice.
Well, what if I got you
another backup band?
Wait, I know who I can get.
They're hot.
Please?
Deej, get a grip.
Actually, loosen your grip.
- Alright, I'm there for you.
- Oh, thank you.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Oh, Kevin,
I missed your entrance.
Could you go back out
and come back in again?
Dad. Kevin's mom is waiting.
And don't you dare follow us
out to the car. Bye.
Thanks for asking me out, Steph.
My pleasure.
Any little brothers
like you at home?
Steph.
Adios, Tanners.
Jesse, be there by 7:00.
The gig pays $50.
But since you don't have
a whole band, you get $20.
Everybody sing.
I gotta go get ready
for the band.
Wait, you are missing
the best part!
[instrumental music]
[piano music]
Hey, Deej, is your backup band
gonna show up or what?
Oh, they'll be here,
don't worry.
Uh, and just remember, you
promised to play no matter what.
I got a feeling I'm gonna
earn my $20 tonight.
So, Kathy, who'd you bring
to the dance?
Him, him and him.
Where'd Kevin go?
He's, um..
Kevin, come over here.
I'm just gonna get some punch.
Want any?
Hey, Kevin,
who asked you here?
D.J.
So how come
your babe's not here?
She's busy talking.
She knows everybody.
I'm not good at that.
- You gotta loosen up, man.
- Yeah.
Come on, we got
a little surprise for you.
What're you guys talking about?
Just come on.
[march music]
[crowd cheering]
D.J. Tanner,
report to the stage immediately.
Oh, great, the band's here.
[imitating D.J.]
Oh, great. The band's..
This is a marching band.
Unless we're playing on a float,
I'm out of here.
You promised.
You promised
a good backup band.
They're good, they're a band
and they're in back of you.
Just give them a chance, please?
Alright.
But let's get one thing
straight.
We're not spelling out
the school name
during our songs.
- Alright!
- Come here.
Now, as you might have guessed,
this is not Dog Face.
But let's give a big Van Atta
Junior High welcome to..
- No names.
- The No Names.
[applause]
You feeling alright out there?
(together)
Yeah!
We'll take care of that.
Here we go!
[singing "Wild Thing"]
[march music]
♪ Wild thing ♪
♪ You make my heart sing ♪
♪ You make
everything groovy.. ♪
Alright.
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Wild thing
I think I love you ♪
♪ B-but I would like
to know for sure ♪
♪ Wild thing you move me.. ♪
He is not worth 20 bucks.
♪ Everybody two three four ♪
[music continues]
♪ Wild thing ♪
♪ A true wild thing ♪♪
Thank you! Thank you!
[D.J. clapping]
[march music]
Stop! Stop, stop, stop! Stop!
Uncle Jesse! You can stop now,
we found a stereo.
Come on, Deej,
it's our big finish
"Stars and Stripes Forever."
Uncle Jesse, it's over.
Aw.
Alright, rehearsal at my house,
Saturday. Great job, kids.
Kimmy, have you seen Kevin?
Last time I saw him,
he was out in the hall.
[chuckles]
He's probably hiding
from the band.
I'll tell him it's safe
to come back in.
[laughing]
- Kevin.
- Hey, D.J.
- What are you doing out here?
- Just hanging out.
The dance was lame,
so we started our own party.
[instrumental music]
You're drinking beer?
Yeah, it tastes horrible.
Want some?
No, I don't want some.
You guys aren't supposed
to be drinking beer.
Big deal. We're just having
some fun. Try it.
[gasps]
- Cut it out.
- You didn't have to do that.
Look, I'm sorry, D.J.
I'll go get some paper towels.
Why don't you guys
just get out of here?
You are so uncool.
Oh, and you think you're cool?
The dance was lame.
Now we're having a party.
Forget it, D.J.,
we don't want any beer.
Yeah, we're only 13.
- D.J. Tanner.
- Uncle Jesse--
You're in big,
big trouble, young lady.
[instrumental music]
Uncle Jesse,
I didn't do anything.
- Oh, yeah? Then what's this?
- It's beer, but--
Hello, what were you gonna
tell me you weren't drinking it?
I can smell it all over you.
Those guys
were the ones drinking.
- I was trying to stop them.
- Alright, save it.
I saw the whole thing.
Come on, you're going home.
- Uncle Jesse.
- D.J., where're you going?
- Home. She doesn't feel well.
- Ugh!
♪ Baby Beluga ♪
Baby Beluga, are you sick?
Uh-oh. Help!
Help!
Honey, what's wrong?
Baby Beluga is broken.
Really?
- Well, maybe I can fix it.
- No.
I want "Baby Beluga."
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
♪ Baby Beluga
in the deep blue sea.. ♪♪
Stop!
Sing it nicely.
♪ Baby Beluga
in the deep blue sea ♪
♪ He swims so wild
and he swims so.. ♪♪
- Dad!
- Danny!
- I'm talking to him first.
- No, I'm talking to him first.
- I am. You don't even know--
- I am--
Whoa! What's going on here?
I was not drinking beer.
- You were not drinking what?
- Danny, I saw the whole thing.
She had a beer in her hand,
She's waving around.
She's talking about partying.
The other kids were drinking.
I was telling them
how stupid they looked.
Hey, Deej,
everybody makes mistakes.
And we know how hard it is
when the other kids are drinking
and they offer you a tri--
I know drinking is wrong.
We already had this talk.
That's why I didn't do it.
I'm telling you the truth.
Right, like you were tellin' us
the truth about your homework?
You weren't
exactly honest about this
marching backup band tonight.
That was totally different.
You believe me, don't you, dad?
I'd like to,
but you do smell like beer.
Someone spilled it
on me, really.
D.J., go to your room.
I'm gonna talk to Jesse and then
I'll come up and talk to you.
This is so unfair.
How could you take his side
instead of believing
your own daughter?
♪ Baby Beluga ♪
♪ Baby Belu.. ♪♪
Oh, no. Get out,
get out, get out!
How could they do this?
I was telling the truth.
I don't deserve
to be treated this way.
I didn't do anything.
What didn't you do?
[sighs]
It doesn't matter,
nobody believes me anyway.
Not Uncle Jesse,
not Joey, ugh, not even dad.
[sobbing]
I believe you, D.J.
You do?
Of course I do.
You're my big sister.
And besides that, you were
looking right in my eyes.
When you lie,
you look at the top of my head.
Thanks, Steph.
I've gotta find a way
for them to believe me.
I can't believe
this is happening.
She's only 13
and she's such a good kid.
Danny, this could happen
to any kid, there's..
There's a lot of pressure
on them to try drinking.
I know,
and not just from other kids.
From, and it's sometimes
these celebrities and rock stars
and people
these kids look up to.
I mean, they're-they're making
drinking look cool.
I mean, they're sending
the wrong message to kids.
But I'll tell you something,
D.J.'s gonna get
the right message,
okay, she's gotta know
that there's no drinking,
period, and I'd say we go
upstairs and lay down the law.
Jesse, wait a minute.
Just sit down.
I-I think it's not as simple
as just punishing her.
I think we have to find out
why D.J. did it
so we can decide
the best way to help her.
I just don't want her
to be one of those kids
who has to learn the hard way.
Your attention, please.
Whatever it is you said D.J.
did, she did not do.
- How do you know, Steph?
- Because she was crying.
And those were not
I'm-in-trouble tears.
Those were
I-really-didn't-do-it tears.
I think we have to straighten
this out right now.
- Yep.
- She's not in her room.
Where is she?
She went back to the dance
with Kimmy's mom
to prove she's innocent.
Oh, great, now she sneaks out
of the house without telling us?
What is going on with her?
Look, you guys,
I'll handle everything here.
- Go ahead, take off.
- Thanks, Joey.
Bye, dad.
I'll see you
at school tomorrow. Bye.
D.J., you missed everything.
Kevin and Paul and Sam
got caught drinking.
They're gonna be suspended
from school.
I hate to say it,
but they deserve it.
Your mom's waiting outside.
I have to find Kevin.
He's over there waiting
for his parents.
You better talk to him now.
You may not see him
for a long time.
- Hi.
You and I have to talk.
My family thinks I was drinking.
Oh, man.
You gotta tell my dad
I'm innocent.
Why did you have to go
and drink, anyway?
Those guys said
it would loosen me up.
I thought you'd have
more fun with me.
Well, I didn't have fun
with you tonight.
I had fun with the old Kevin.
Kevin, your parents are here.
I'm dead.
D.J., I'm really sorry.
I know you are.
Is it okay
if I call you again sometime?
Alright, just make sure
the old Kevin calls.
Come on, son. Let's go.
Kevin, have you seen D.J.?
- Yeah. She's in there.
- Thanks.
- Uh, Mr. Tanner?
- Yeah?
D.J. wasn't drinking tonight.
It was me and two other guys.
She was trying to stop us.
She was telling us the truth.
I'm sorry, man. I-I saw her
with the beer, I just--
Oh, no, Jess, don't feel bad.
It was an honest mistake.
Thanks for telling us, Kevin.
Come on, Kevin.
Come on, let's go.
I was pretty rough on her.
Do you mind if I go in
and have a word alone with D.J.?
Okay.
Hi.
Oh, great.
Now I'm in even more trouble.
Look, I came down here
to find Kevin so that--
I just talked to Kevin outside.
- You did?
- Yeah.
He told me what really happened.
I owe you a big apology.
You really hurt my feelings.
I'm sorry
for not believing you, pal.
Well, I guess
it did look kind of bad.
And I did bend the truth
a couple times this week.
D.J., I want you to know
why I lost my temper tonight.
It just, it made me crazy
thinking of my little niece
out there starting to drink.
I mean, this isn't fun
and games, you know, I've seen
it happen to my friends,
they think they have it
in their control,
before they know it
they'd messed up
their whole lives.
That's why I'm so proud of you
for making
the right decision tonight.
It's not that hard to say no.
Those kids
were acting like idiots.
Well..
...we made it
through tonight.
The sad truth
is that you're gonna be faced
with a lot
of tough decisions in your life.
And not just about drinking,
either, about..
About drugs, and about sex..
...and...who knows what.
[dramatic music]
I just wish
you could grow up in a world
where you can enjoy
being a kid.
But I'm sorry, pal,
that's not the way it is.
So...I hope that
you'll use
the same good judgment
that you used tonight.
Because I never want
to see you get hurt.
I love you so much.
I love you too,
Uncle Jesse. Thank you.
Alright, let's go home, huh?
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪♪